

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

JANEIL CARROLL

Hi, I'm Janeil — a versatile graphic designer exploring full-stack development. Beyond design, I excel in entrepreneurship and express my love of the arts as a professional musician. Let's connect creativity with technical expertise and build something great together.

CONTACT

1-709-219-2491

janeilchantelle@gmail.com

Portugal Cove - St. Philips, NL

EDUCATION

KEYIN COLLEGE 2023-2024

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT

 Currently enrolled in a fully scholarship-funded Software Development Diploma program.

ACADEMY CANADA 2005-2007

MULTIMEDIA GRAPHIC DESIGN

 Completed a dynamic two-year program in Multimedia Graphic
Design, mastering industry-standard design tools and gaining proficiency in creating visually impactful content.

EXPERIENCE

WICKED KITCHEN 2020 - 2023



OWNER | OPERATOR

Founded and operated Wicked Kitchen, a successful venture in the niche market of vegan cuisine. Developed a comprehensive business plan, orchestrated the launch of an ecommerce platform, and maintained sales across six local retail stores and online channels. Oversaw all aspects of the business, including brand identity, social media management, accounting, marketing, and production. Demonstrated a hands-on approach to entrepreneurship by effectively managing every facet of Wicked Kitchen's operations, ensuring its growth and prominence in the vegan food market.



GRAPHIC DESIGNER

JANEIL CARROLL

Hi, I'm Janeil — a versatile graphic designer exploring full-stack development. Beyond design, I excel in entrepreneurship and express my love of the arts as a professional musician. Let's connect creativity with technical expertise and build something great together.

CONTACT

1-709-219-2491

janeilchantelle@gmail.com

Portugal Cove - St. Philips, NL

EDUCATION

KEYIN COLLEGE 2023-2024

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT

 Currently enrolled in a fully scholarship-funded Software
Development Diploma program.

ACADEMY CANADA 2005-2007

MULTIMEDIA GRAPHIC DESIGN

 Completed a dynamic two-year program in Multimedia Graphic
Design, mastering industry-standard design tools and gaining proficiency in creating visually impactful content.

EXPERIENCE

WICKED KITCHEN 2020 - 2023



OWNER | OPERATOR

Founded and operated Wicked Kitchen, a successful venture in the niche market of vegan cuisine. Developed a comprehensive business plan, orchestrated the launch of an ecommerce platform, and maintained sales across six local retail stores and online channels. Oversaw all aspects of the business, including brand identity, social media management, accounting, marketing, and production. Demonstrated a hands-on approach to entrepreneurship by effectively managing every facet of Wicked Kitchen's operations, ensuring its growth and prominence in the vegan food market.

SKILLS

Graphic Design

Web Design

Full-Stack

Development

UI/UX Design

Entrepreneurship

E-commerce

Management

Professional

Musician

Creativity

Software

Development

Project

Management

Communication

Problem-Solving

Team Collaboration

Time Management

Client Relations

Marketing

Branding

Adaptability



JANEIL CHANTELLE 2007 - PRESENT



FREELANCE DESIGNER

Versatile freelance designer with a keen eye for aesthetics and a passion for creating impactful visual experiences. Proficient in graphic and web design, I bring creativity and adaptability to every project, ensuring tailored solutions that captivate and communicate effectively.

IMPACT SIGNS & GRAOHICS LTD

2016 - 2019



GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Experienced graphic designer at Impact Signs and Graphics, known for creating captivating print designs, corporate signage and vehicle wraps. I've collaborated with notable clients such as the Government of NL, the Royal Newfoundland Constabulary, and the George Street Association. Proficient in Adobe Creative Suite and Corel Draw, my work reflects a wealth of experience in delivering creative solutions tailored to a diverse clientele.

BUY & SELL MAGAZINE

2014 - 2016



GRAPHIC DESIGNER

"As the Senior Graphic Designer at the Buy and Sell Magazine, I led the design of compelling advertisements for businesses and played a key role in the layout and launch of the magazine. Additionally, I provided design solutions for businesses, creating collateral such as business cards, brochures, and pamphlets. This role showcased my leadership, creativity, and versatility in delivering impactful visual content across various mediums."